

Tanav Bajaj

tanav.bajaj58@gmail.com 🔀

9814062001

Ludhiana, India

tanav2202.github.io/

linkedin.com/in/tanav-bajaj in

github.com/tanav2202

Tech enthusiast with a love for reading and an Undergraduate student at IIIT Bhopal and IIT Madras. Also one of the Leads at IIITian Network (Student community). I enjoy meeting new people and discussing ideas on topics of mutual interest. I have had amazing experiences there from being incharge of various inter/intra school projects to holding positions of responsibility at ages 16 (President) and 14(Head boy) which gave me the necessary skills to be a team leader and a team player.

EDUCATION

BTech

Indian Institute Of Information Technology

2020 - 2024 Bhopal

Courses

 BTech in Information Technology

D BSc.

Indian Institute Of Technology

2021 - 2024 Madras

Courses

 BSc In Programming And Data Science

PROJECTS

Project Comet Website (03/2021)

 Fixed some pages and components in Design and Coding of Project Comet Labs (A Start-up) Website

IIITians Network Website (05/2021 - Present)

 Rebranding of The official Website of IIITians Network. The main task that I have been working on is to Design the new website and switch it to the MERN stack

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Manager

IIITians Network

06/2021 - Present

Student Community For all IIITs where we learn and grow together

Responsibility

 I am in-charge of Internal Management of the Network and making sure all teams work together efficiently

FrontEnd Developer

IIITians Network

05/2021 - Present

Student Community For all IIITs where we learn and grow together

Achievements/Tasks

Working On the Rebranding Of the Network Website

O Designer

IIITians Network

02/2021 - Present

Student Community For all IIITs where we learn and grow together

Achievements/Tasks

 Worked as Web Designer for a tentative Event Code Chronicles of IIITians Network

SKILLS

Web Development (Baiscs)

UI/UX Design

Leadership

Communication Skills

Public Speaking

ACHIEVEMENTS

Group Leader and In-charge of Tech Team Sunderbans House

IIT Madras created Student Communities and divided the students in Various houses. I (after winning elections) became a group leader of about 20 students and also in-charge of the Tech team of the entire house.

CERTIFICATES

Google IT Support (07/2020 - 09/2020)

During the time of COVID and before College began I studied the skills needed for being an IT support specialist by doing this course on Coursera

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency

Puniabi

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading Fictional books and Biographies

Web Development and Design

Trying New Cuisines

Meeting New People